[
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "13A_Maria",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What was the Shattering?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "A time of much sorrow, when the world was trampled by the Lost. \\n\\nThe Corpse Crone still haunts the southwestern fen. Don’t bother with the silkweed there. You’ll be better off gathering hemp from the western fields.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "13A_Agnes",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Maybe you haven’t met the right man?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "After 500 years, you gotta face the possibility that there may be no such thing. There are plenty of oversized children, loudmouthed braggarts, and the eternally confused, however. \\n\\nTake home a candle instead. It's warmth, no drama.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "13A_Theuderic",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Is it serious?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Yes, very. Catch it and you’ll turn Lost in a week. Luckily, I have found a cure. \\n\\nTheuderic Julietti at your service! For only 100 coin, I’ll sneak you the right card in this game of life.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "13A_Niall",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Did she eat something bad?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Haha, this darling should stick to rabbits. But she's got a taste for humans. Imagine someone chasing you for your skin. \\n\\nThe poor darling probably gets scared. She just shouldn't eat me again, silly girl.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "13A_Theo_FactionRival",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'm in the Syndicate, too.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Wunderbar! A fellow seeker of truth! In my opinion, the Syndicate is the only rational faction choice. \\n\\nThough, I do wish we could devote more resources to research, and less to warfare…",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "13A_Theo_FactionSame",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'm not a Syndicate member.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I see. I suppose we must fight. \\n\\nIt would be quite inconvenient for me to die right now. If you must kill me, could you monitor my experiment until I return? \\n\\nOh, you won't attack? Then there is no problem!",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "13A_HunterJulio_Repellent",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Do you know how to make bear repellent?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Bear repellent? Sure, easy enough. There's an old recipe that hunters here have used for ages. Here, take it. \\n\\nThose Syndicate folk…if you ask me, they're so concerned with being logical they forget to be practical.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "13A_ResearcherPiper_Repellent",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I, uh, have something for you.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Wow, urine! Just what I needed!",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "13A_ResearcherLing_Repellent",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Do you need some bear repellent?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Did Theo finally figure out the formula? Thank science for that…",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "13A_ResearcherRinde_Repellent",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Surprise! I made you some bear repellent.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Ugh, this smells terrible. \\n\\nThe things I do for data...",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "13A_ResearcherLubin_Repellent",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I have some bear repellent for you.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Ah, it's almost a shame. I think the bears were about to accept me, maybe.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    }
]
